1. Define abstract class Shape with only one abstract method CalculateSurface() and fields width and height. Define two new classes Triangle and Rectangle that implement the virtual method and return the surface of the figure (height*width for rectangle and height*width/2 for triangle). Define class Circle and suitable constructor so that at initialization height must be kept equal to width and implement the CalculateSurface() method. Write a program that tests the behavior of  the CalculateSurface() method for different shapes (Circle, Rectangle, Triangle) stored in an array.

2. A bank holds different types of accounts for its customers: deposit accounts, loan accounts and mortgage accounts. Customers could be individuals or companies.
  All accounts have customer, balance and interest rate (monthly based). Deposit accounts are allowed to deposit and with draw money. Loan and mortgage accounts can only deposit money.
  All accounts can calculate their interest amount for a given period (in months). In the common case its is calculated as follows: number_of_months * interest_rate.
Loan accounts have no interest for the first 3 months if are held by individuals and for the first 2 months if are held by a company.
Deposit accounts have no interest if their balance is positive and less than 1000.
Mortgage accounts have ½ interest for the first 12 months for companies and no interest for the first 6 months for individuals.
Your task is to write a program to model the bank system by classes and interfaces. You should identify the classes, interfaces, base classes and abstract actions and implement the calculation of the interest functionality through overridden methods.

3. Define a class InvalidRangeException<T> that holds information about an error condition related to invalid range. It should hold error message and a range definition [start … end].
  Write a sample application that demonstrates the InvalidRangeException<int> and InvalidRangeException<DateTime> by entering numbers in the range [1..100] and dates in the range [1.1.1980 … 31.12.2013].
